huckberry.com 2018-12-21

# Privacy Policy | Huckberry

Privacy Policy Updated on May 24th, 2018

* * *

Huckberry.com has developed this privacy policy to let you know how we collect and use the personal information you provide to us while visiting our web site (the "Site"). By visiting the Site and/or signing up for membership registration, you accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

The Privacy Policy explains our online and offline information practices, the types of information we collect, and what we do with that information. All terms in this Privacy Policy carry the same meaning is in our Terms of Service.

##### Information We Collect

We collect information for the primary reason of improving your customer experience and enabling Services both online and offline. There are two main ways Huckberry may collect Personal Information. We strive to only collect Personal Information which is relevant for the purposes of Processing.

  * You may provide your personal information directly to us: This may happen while creating an account or in the checkout process
  * As you navigate through Huckberry.com, we may collect certain passive information about your site visit through the use of cookies, pixel tags, local storage, and other technologies

**More Details**

We collect personally identifying information that you provide us during the registration process, such as your name, email address, gender, zip code and date of birth. We also collect personal identifying information when you choose to use certain other features of the Site, such as when you order a product or service from us or our partners, and when you otherwise volunteer personal information about yourself, for example, through surveys, contests or promotions, and submitting and/or posting content in discussion forums. When you choose to use these additional features, we may require you to provide additional personal information such as your phone number, billing and shipping addresses and credit card information.

In addition, through the Site, we automatically gather certain non-personally identifiable information about the use of the Site, such as how frequently certain areas of the Site are visited, including through the use of cookies, pixel tags, local storage, and other technologies. This gives us valuable information about your customer shopping experience and is used only to improve your experience with our website. Most browsers can be set to prevent cookies or to notify you when one is being placed. It is not necessary to have cookies turned on to visit our Site, but without them, your access to some areas may be limited and certain features, including shopping and purchasing features, may not be available to you.

##### Third-Party Payment Processing

When you make purchases through the Services, we process your payments through a Third-Party application. The Third-Party application may collect certain financial information from you to process a payment on behalf of Huckberry, including your name, email address, address and other billing information.

##### How We Use Your Information

We use your personally identifiable information to support and enhance your use of the Site and its features, including without limitation: fulfilling your order; providing customer service; tracking email invitations you send; and otherwise supporting your use of the Site and its features. We may also track your past purchases to provide you with a personalized profile of your purchase history. The personal information you provide to us will also be added to our databases and used for future communications regarding new product offerings or other special promotions.

Huckberry may use your data in any of the following two ways.

  * Providing you with products or services. Huckberry may use information to fulfill orders or for information that may be included for future services such as processing orders or any other services Huckberry may provide.
  * Marketing for Huckberry.com and Huckberry Products. Huckberry may use your Personal Information to market you offers, products, and Services. Huckberry may provide you with these materials by postal mail, email, as permitted by applicable law. Huckberry may also share your Personal Information with other organizations that send you materials by postal mail.

**More Details**

In addition to email communication, we may also use your Personal Information (such as your name, postal address and shopping history) to contact you with marketing and promotional materials, or other information we feel may be of interest to you. Some of these materials may be sent via a third party service provider. The information shared with third party service providers may be used to supplement like-minded organizations direct mail marketing programs. No personal information is shared outside our third-party providers, and Huckberry does not receive payment for any information shared with these vendors.

If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive direct mail communications from Huckberry, you can can unsubscribe by clicking [here](http://goo.gl/forms/OVepLvR00x) and filling out the unsubscribe form, or by emailing us at support@huckberry.com. Furthermore, if you decide that you would like to continue receiving direct mail communications from Huckberry, but would like to opt-out of sharing your information with like-minded organizations, please by clicking [here](http://goo.gl/forms/OVepLvR00x) and filling out the form or email us at [support@huckberry.com](mailto:support@huckberry.com).

By registering with Huckberry.com, you are automatically subscribed to our email, but may choose to opt out of our email list at any time. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive email communications from us, you can can unsubscribe by clicking [here](https://huckberry.com/account/preferences) and updating your email preferences, or by emailing us at [support@huckberry.com](mailto:support@huckberry.com).

Live in the EU? We have updated our site in compliance of the new GDPR regulations. Any questions or data requests can be sent to [support@huckberry.com](mailto:support@huckberry.com). Please use the subject line “Privacy” and we will be more than happy to fulfill your needs.

##### Third-Party Advertising Partners + Internet Advertising Programs

We use cookies, pixel tags, local storage, and other technologies on our site to supplement the overall site experience. In addition, we use Third Parties that also use cookies and other technologies on our site, that allow us to connect with social media, serve ads and more services. The use of cookies allows us to place a small data file on our site that allows us to better understand how a user interacts with our site across multiple devices, channels and more. These cookies or pixel tags are used for services such as:

  * Analytics: We use Google Analytics, a service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”), to gather information about how users engage with our Services. For more information about Google Analytics, please visit www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/. You can opt out of Google’s collection and processing of data generated by your use of the Services by going to http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout. We use other analytics providers such as Segment and Quantcast to gather information on how users interact with our site
  * Google User-ID: This allows us to more accurately track and compile information from various sessions and tie them to a single anonymous user ID
  * Social Media Widgets: We use social sharing widgets through Sumo, by Sumo Inc., that allows users to share via social network, directly from huckberry.com
  * Augmented Site Functionality: We use various Third Party Providers that allow us to enhance the site experience. This includes Reviews functionality by Yotpo, Inc., Search functionality by Algolia, Inc., and more.
  * Site Performance Information: We use performance monitoring software that allows us to understand user traffic levels on our site and receive alerts when traffic levels increase or errors arise on the site
  * Advertising & Targeting: We use advertising software to surface ads to users who have visited huckberry.com

**More Details**

We use third-party service providers to serve advertisements (image banners or links) on our behalf across the Internet. These advertising service providers may collect non-identifiable information about your visits to our website, and your online interactions with certain products and services. Such non-identifiable information does not include your name, address, email address or other personal information. The information is collected through the use of cookies, pixel tags, local storage, and other technologies, which is industry-standard technology used by many major websites.

In addition to the information about your visits to our website, our service providers may also use the information about your visits to other websites to target advertisements for products and services available from Huckberry. Huckberry may work with other companies in the future to provide interest-based advertising, both on and off Huckberry.com. If so, Huckberry will provide you with the opportunity to opt-out when these advertisements are served.

If you would like to learn more about Interest-based advertising, and to know your choices for not having this information used by third-party service providers, please visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

##### Third-Party Platform Advertising

We may also use platforms provided by companies such as Google and Facebook to offer you interest-based ads. These platforms allow us to personalize the ads that we display to you. We do not share any of your personal information, including your shopping history, with these platform vendors. Huckberry may convert your email address into a unique value which can be matched by our partner companies with a user on their platform to allow us to present you with interest-based advertising. Although we do not provide any personal information to these platform vendors, they may gain insights about individuals who respond to the ads we serve. You may learn more about Interest-based advertising, and to know your choices for not having this information used by third-party service providers by clicking [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

##### Access to Personal Information

We may permit certain trusted third parties to access your information in connection with their performance of services to maintain and operate the Site and certain features on the Site. For example, we may use third parties to host the Site; operate various features available on the Site; send emails; analyze data; provide search results and links and assist in fulfilling your orders.

To provide services you have requested, it may be necessary to provide your personal information to Huckberry merchants and or service providers in order to aid redemption of services requested. Logistics services may utilize supplied information only for completing your delivery.

We may transfer personally identifiable information as an asset in connection with a proposed or actual merger or sale (including any transfers made as part of an insolvency or bankruptcy proceeding) involving all or part of our business or as part of a corporate reorganization, stock sale, membership transfer, or other change in control.

If you use a bulletin board, chat room, product reviews or any other publicly accessible area of the Site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected or used by any person for any purpose. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable or other information you choose to submit in these forums.

Additionally, we may provide links on our Site to websites controlled by third parties. We have no control over these websites and our privacy policy does not apply to these third party websites. Please consult the privacy policy of the website you are visiting.

Huckberry.com does not sell, rent, loan or otherwise allow third party access to your information except as set forth above.

##### How We Protect Your Information

We are committed to protecting the information we receive from you. We follow reasonable technical and management practices to help protect the confidentiality, security and integrity of data stored on our system. While no computer system is completely secure, we believe the measures we have implemented reduce the likelihood of security problems to a level appropriate to the type of data involved.

The Site uses security measures in order to protect from the loss, misuse and alteration of any information under our control. All orders are transmitted over secure internet connections using SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) encryption technology. In addition, only those employees and third parties who need access to your information in order to perform their duties are allowed such access.

#### Updating and Correcting Information

##### Your Data Rights

We will always respect your rights to limit or exclude the data you share with us. We offer you choices regarding the Personal Information we collect and share from you. Please understand that if you do limit the Personal Information you share with us, you may not be able to access all the features or Services at Huckberry.

Here are the areas we collect Personal Information for that you may submit requests for:

  * Email
  * Physical Mail
  * Human Resources
  * Cookies & Session Information
  * Internet-Based Advertising

You may withdraw your consent, request a copy of your personal data, modify what data we collect or request that we delete the data we have collected from you by reaching out to support@huckberry.com with the subject “Privacy”.

Huckberry will do everything in our control to meet the your Personal Information requests. There may be circumstances where we are unable to meet those demands, including but not limited to: where the information contains legal privilege, would compromise others’ privacy or other legitimate rights, where the burden or expense of providing access would be disproportionate to the risks to the Individual’s privacy in the case in question or where it is commercially proprietary.

If Huckberry determines that access should be restricted in any particular instance, we will provide you with an explanation of why that determination has been made and a contact point for any further inquiries.

##### Data Retention

Huckberry retains Personal Information provided by site visitors, as described in this Privacy Policy, for as long as you use our Services or as necessary to fulfill the purpose(s) for which it was collected. In addition, we may use or disclose personal information in the good faith belief that we are lawfully required to do so, or that doing so is reasonably necessary to protect you, to comply with legal process or the instructions of legal authorities, to respond to any claims, to enforce our legal rights, or to protect the rights, property or personal safety of ourselves, our employees, you, or members of the public.

##### Security of Your Information

The security and privacy of you Personal Information is important to us and we take necessary and reasonable measures to protect your data. When you enter your Personal Information in our forms we encrypt this data through SSL or other technologies. Please understand that transmitting or storing data on the internet is not completely secure and we cannot guarantee absolute security of any information.

##### International Users

Site visitors from countries outside of the United States, including the European Union, should understand that any data provided to Huckberry may be transferred to the United States. By choosing to visit our Site, engage in our Services or otherwise provide information to us, you agree that any dispute arising in connection with Huckberry will be in accordance with the Terms.

##### Children's Privacy and Parental Controls

We do not solicit any personal information from children. If you are not 18 or older, you are not authorized to use the Site. Parents should be aware that there are parental control tools available online that you can use to prevent your children from submitting information online without parental permission or from accessing material that is harmful to minors.

##### Changes to This Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy for the Site, we will post the revised Privacy Policy here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and whether we may disclose it to anyone. Your continued use of the Site indicates your assent to the Privacy Policy as posted. We last modified this privacy policy on May 24, 2018, which is the effective date of this policy.

##### Your California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits our Members who are California residents to request and obtain from us once a year, free of charge, information about the personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year. If applicable, this information would include a list of the categories of personal information that was shared and the names and addresses of all third parties with which we shared information in the immediately preceding calendar year. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit your request in writing to the address shown below.

##### How to reach us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at:

Huckberry  
290 Utah St.  
San Francisco, CA 94103  
+1 (855) 325-8998  

Last Updated: May 24, 2018. ©2018 Huckberry Inc. All rights reserved.
